Samson Peter O.

UI/UX Designer | Frontend Developer

EXPERIENCES

Kony Developer

(Prema-Consulting, Amman Jordan)

June 2022-Present

- Development and customization of Temenos infinity products using Quantum Kony visualizer IDE.
- Development of themes, designs and template using Kony, API integration using Fabrics, E2E testing etc.

Senior Technical Consultant

(ITSS GLOBAL, Geneva, Switzerland)

2022

- Development and customization of Temenos infinity products using Quantum Kony visualizer IDE.
- Development and customization of TCIB (Temenos Connect Internet banking) using Temenos UXP.
- Development of themes, designs and template using UXP, Iris & Swagger API integration, E2E testing etc.

Infinity UI/UX Developer

(ITSS GLOBAL, Geneva, Switzerland)

2021-2022

- Development and customization of Temenos infinity products using Quantum Kony visualizer IDE.
- Development and customization of TCIB (Temenos Connect Internet banking) using Temenos UXP.
- Development of themes, designs and template using UXP.

Frontend Developer

(Xpress Payments Solutions Limited, Lagos, Nigeria) 2020-Feb. 2021

- Design of modern, responsive and interactive User Interface mock-ups.
- Development of dynamic, enterprise-based web apps using modern frontend frameworks and technologies.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering (B.Eng.)

Second Class Upper Honors.

Agricultural Engineering

Federal University of Technology, Akure. 2018

CERTIFICATES

- 2019 Project Management Professional (PMP)
 British Project Management Academy, UK.
- 2019 Certificate of Achievement (Quality Mgt.)
 Rahn Wesley Institute of Management, UK.
 - **2019 Certificate of National Service**National Youth Service Corps (NYSC).

5, Matanmi close, Oko-Filling, Alagbado, Lagos State.

Mobile: (+234) 8164224586.

Portfoliolivingstone 17. github.io/myportfolio.github.io

Github: https://github.com/livingstone17 Email: Peterson.omobolaji@gmail.com LinkedIn: /peter-samson-38202614b

Born: 26 April, 1994. Nationality: Nigerian.

SUMMARY

Meticulous UI/UX designer and frontend developer with hands on experience in designing and developing enterprise-based platforms with passion for responsive design and thorough believer of the mobile first approach. Implemented state-of-the-art responsive websites and optimized existing ones.

Knowledgeable in designing and building simple, interactive and modern user interfaces, user testing and debugging process.

Ability to effectively self-manage during independent project as well as collaborating in a team setting, with thorough understanding of the agile project management principle.

SKILLS

JavaScript Intermediate HTML5 Advanced Bootstrap Advanced CSS3 Expert Kony Visualizer Temenos UXP Git Intermediate MongoDB Intermediate Agile (SCRUM) Expert iQuery Intermediate React.JS Intermediate Angular Intermediate Node.JS Beginner Adobe Photoshop Intermediate Adobe XD Intermediate Figma Intermediate Microsoft Packages Expert Tailwind CSS Intermediate SASS Intermediate Material UI Intermediate Mocha/Chai.js Beginner

LANGUAGES

English Expert
Yoruba Native
Nigerian Pidain Intermediate